[
    {
        "lessonId": "4",
        "title": "Lesson 4",
        "exercises": [
  {
    "front": "he eats",
    "back_hint": "ya'kul",
    "back": "يَأْكُل",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "yesterday",
    "back_hint": "ams",
    "back": "أَمْس",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "first",
    "back_hint": "awwal",
    "back": "أَوَّل",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "\"primary, elementary\"",
    "back_hint": "ibtidayiyy / ibtidayiyya",
    "back": "اِبْتِدائِيّ / اِبْتِدائِيّة",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "I memorize",
    "back_hint": "ahfadh",
    "back": "أَحْفَظ",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "\"sweets, desserts\"",
    "back_hint": "halawiyat / huluw",
    "back": "حَلَوِيّات، حُلو",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "vegetables",
    "back_hint": "khudhaar",
    "back": "خُضار",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "school",
    "back_hint": "madrasa / madaris",
    "back": "مَدْرَسة / مَدارِس",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "I remember",
    "back_hint": "atadhakkar",
    "back": "أَتَذَكَّر",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "\"classmate, colleague (masc.)\"",
    "back_hint": "zamil zumalaa'",
    "back": "زَميل ج زُمَلاء",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "\"classmate, colleague (fem.)\"",
    "back_hint": "zamila / zamilat",
    "back": "زَميلة / زَميلات",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "\"travelling from, to (noun)\"",
    "back_hint": "as safar min / ila",
    "back": "السَّفَر مِن، إلى",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "I travel to",
    "back_hint": "usafir ila",
    "back": "أُسافِر إلى",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "salad",
    "back_hint": "salata / salatat",
    "back": "سَلَطة / سَلَطات",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "he listens to",
    "back_hint": "yastami' ila",
    "back": "يَسْتَمِع إلى",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "fish",
    "back_hint": "samak",
    "back": "سَمَك",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "soup",
    "back_hint": "shurba",
    "back": "شُورْبة",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "friend (masc.)",
    "back_hint": "sadiq 'asdiqa'",
    "back": "صَديق ج أَصْدِقاء",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "friend (fem.)",
    "back_hint": "sadiqa sadiqat",
    "back": "صَديقة ج صَديقات",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "childhood",
    "back_hint": "at tufuula",
    "back": "الطُّفولة",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "restaurant",
    "back_hint": "mat'am / mataa'im",
    "back": "مَطْعَم / مَطاعِم",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "\"individual, person\"",
    "back_hint": "fard / 'afraad",
    "back": "فَرْد / أَفْراد",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "fruit",
    "back_hint": "fakiha / fawaakih",
    "back": "فاكِهة / فَواكِه",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "before (with a noun or participle)",
    "back_hint": "qabla + ism",
    "back": "قَبْلَ + اسم",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "he reads",
    "back_hint": "yaqra'",
    "back": "يَقرأ",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "he says",
    "back_hint": "yaqul",
    "back": "يَقول",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "he writes",
    "back_hint": "yaktub",
    "back": "يَكْتُب",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "all of the ... (with a following plural)",
    "back_hint": "kull + al jam'",
    "back": "كُلّ + الجمع",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "he was",
    "back_hint": "kaana",
    "back": "كانَ",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "I was",
    "back_hint": "kuntu",
    "back": "كُنْتُ",
    "lesson": "4"
  },
  {
    "front": "meat",
    "back_hint": "lahm",
    "back": "لَحم",
    "lesson": "4"
  }
]
  
    }
]